Finding Aid for BMC Media Services records, 1851-2003
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Topical Files
  - Medical Related Topical Files
    - Year of Older Persons Celebration, 1999 (Box 19)
    - Gerontology
      - Award Presentation, 1991 (Box 19)
      - Future of Research in Aging, undated (Box 19)
      - Luncheon and Lecture, 1994 (Box 19)
      - Tribute to Wilma Donahue, 1993 (Box 19)
    - Gifts of Art, 1990 (Box 19)
    - Graduation Ceremonies, negatives
      - 1967 (Box 19)
      - 1968 (Box 19)
      - 1969 (Box 19)
      - 1970 (Box 19)
    - Groups -- Unidentified, undated (Box 19)
    - Health Services
      - Health Services Staff, 2000 (Box 19)
      - Moderate Drinking Campaign, 1998 (Box 19)
    - Heart Care
      - Handheld Unit, 1997 (Box 19)
      - Stampede of Races, 2000 (Box 19)
    - Heart Station, 1955 (Box 19)
    - Hematology and Oncology
      - Brochure, 1989; 2 folders (Box 19)
      - Drs. Baker and Bierman, 1999 (Box 19)
    - Horizons, 1990; 1991 (Box 19)
    - Hospital scenes, various dates, unidentified, slides, prints and negatives (Box 19)
    - Howard Hughes Medical Institute (HHMI)
      - Anatomy Brochure, Undated (Box 19)
      - Dr. Wilson
        - Dr. Wilson and Marrianne in Lab, Dr. Wilson and Jasmin, 1992 (Box 19)
        - Dr. Wilson, Assistant and Rabbit, 1990 (Box 19)
        - Jim and Marrianne with Rabbits, 1992 (Box 19)
        - With Patient, 1992 (Box 19)
      - Environment Portraits, 1992 (Box 19)
      - Genetically Altered Mice, 1999 (Box 19)
      - Genetically Designed Mouse, 1999 (Box 19)
      - Group Portrait, 1991 (Box 19)
      - Informal Group Shot, 1990 (Box 19)
      - Interiors -- Human Applications Laboratory, 1992 (Box 19)
      - Nabel for P.R. Department, 1992 (Box 19)
      - Wilson/Grossman Portrait, 1992 (Box 19)
    - Historical Center for Health Sciences, 1994; 2000 (Box 19)
    - Hospital Administration, 1999 (Box 19)
    - Hospital Scenes, various dates (Box 19)
    - Hospital Star newsletters, 1963-1966; undated (Box 19)
      (known as: University Hospital Star, University of Michigan Hospital Star, Hospital Star, Star, University of Michigan Hospitals Star, University of Michigan Medical Center Star, University of Michigan Health System Star)
    - Human Genetics, 1999 (Box 19)
    - Huron Valley Ambulance
      - Ann Arbor School Bus Drivers, 1994 (Box 19)
      - Annual Report, 1994 (Box 19)
      - Group of Paramedics for Newsletter, 1994 (Box 19)
      - HVAC Group, 1993 (Box 19)
      - South Lyon Ambulance Shoot, 1994 (Box 19)
    - Hypertension, 1996 (Box 19)
    - Immunology (prints), undated (Box 19)
    - Institute of Gerontology
      - Interactive Project, 1998 (Box 19)
      - Learning in Retirement, 1999 (Box 19)
      - Retirement Brochure, 1998 (Box 19)
      - Trainee Seminar, 1998 (Box 19)
      - Website, 1998 (Box 19)
    - Internal Medicine
      - Breath Test for Science Magazine, 1993 (Box 19)
      - Brochure
        - Annual Brochure Med Students, 1996 (Box 19)
        - Candids, 1994 (Box 19)
        - House Officer and Fellowship Brochure, 1993 (Box 19)
      - Cancer Center Building, 1996 (Box 19)
      - Conference, 1995 (Box 19)
      - Dr. [Douglas A.] Greene in Clinical Setting, 1999 (Box 19)
      - Dr. Hume AM report, 1996 (Box 19)
      - Dr. Hume and Dr. Montie, Ford Amphitheatre, 1996 (Box 19)
      - Dr. Hume/Grand Rounds, 1996 (Box 19)
      - Dr. Kelly's Last Day, 1989 (Box 19)
      - Dr. Mangrulkar interacting with students, 2001 (Box 19)
      - Dr. Yamada Lab Portrait with Staff, 1991 (Box 19)
      - General Medicine Conference Group, 2000 (Box 19)
      - H. Marvin Pollard Prof. Chung Owyang, 1996 (Box 19)
      - House Officers Conference for Brochure, 1996 (Box 19)
      - Immunology Lab Shots, 1999 (Box 19)
      - Instruments, 1996 (Box 19)
      - Kidney Foundation Candids, 1990 (Box 19)
      - Lab Experiments, 2001 (Box 19)
      - Mary Lou Barden Send Off, 1996 (Box 19)
      - M.M. and G. Core Lab Brochure, 1991 (Box 19)
      - Medical Student Geriatric Photos, 1993 (Box 19)
      - Mice, 1997 (Box 20)
      - Millie Schembechler Conference, 1999 (Box 20)
      - Pre [Post] Doc Recruitment Brochure, 1997 (Box 20)
      - Residency Orientation Booth, 1996 (Box 20)
      - Schembechler Fund Presentation, undated (Box 20)
      - Schembechler Memorial Conference, 1997 (Box 20)
      - Video Screens, 1998 (Box 20)
    - Inteflex
      - Composites
        - First Year and Inteflex Third Year Students, 1984-1985 (Box 20)
        - First Year Students, 1988-1989 (Box 20)
      - Individual Portraits
        - First Year and Inteflex Third Year Students, 1984-1985 (Box 20)
        - (Class of 1999), 1992 (Box 20)
        - 1993 (Box 20)
        - 1995 (Box 20)
        - (Class of 2004), 1996 (Box 20)
        - 1997 (Box 20)
        - 1998 (Box 20)
      - Sampler, 1995 (Box 20)
    - Kellogg Eye Center
      - 125th Year Anniversary, 1997 (Box 20)
      - Brochure, Residency Training, 1995 (Box 20)
      - Dr. Falls Symposium, 1996 (Box 20)
      - Dr. Paul Seiving and MLK Celebration, undated (Box 20)
      - Gronvall Luncheon, 1998 (Box 20)
      - Instruments, 1997 (Box 20)
      - Newsletter, 1995 (Box 20)
      - Offsite Physicians, 1998 (Box 20)
      - Ophthalmology, 1997 (Box 20)
      - Spring Conference, 1996 (Box 20)
    - Laboratories (Identified subjects include: Jane Bradley and Darlene Yatchak) and Microscopes, undated (Box 20)
    - Machines and Equipment (includes artificial kidney, heart pump, x-ray), undated; 2 folders (Box 20)
    - Marketing Communications, 1992 (Box 20)
    - M-Block, 1988-1999 (Box 20)
    - MCare
      - Briefer Drabny (Drs) Location Portraits, 1991; negatives (Box 20)
      - Lowe Ann Arbor News"Back Care", undated; negatives (Box 20)
      - Med Rehab, 1991; negatives (Box 20)
      - New employee portraits for newsletter, 1991; negatives (Box 20)
    - Medical Administration
      - Association of Minority Scientists, 1996 (Box 20)
      - Brochure, 1991
        - Admissions, 1991 (Box 20)
        - Medical School, 1993-1994 (Box 20)
        - Medical Scientist Training Program (MSTP), 1995; 1996 (Box 20)
      - Dr. Judge and Company at Computers, 1993 (Box 20)
      - Education Conference Group and League, 1995 (Box 20)
      - Forum on Health Care Reform with Dr. Reardon, 1994 (Box 20)
      - Honors Convocation photos for brochure, 1991; negatives (Box 20)
      - Medical Center Photos, 1996 (Box 20)
      - Medical School commencement photos for admissions brochure, 1991; negatives (Box 20)
      - Medical Students for brochure print, 1991; negatives (Box 20)
      - Northwest Tour of Holden, 1993 (Box 20)
      - Poster Presentation
        - 1990, negatives (Box 20)
        - 1992 (Box 20)
      - Retirement Party for Margaret Woodbury, undated; negatives (Box 20)
        (Dr Shope presenting UM chair)
      - Student Poster Session, 1989; negatives (Box 20)
    - Medical Center Alumni Society (MCAS)
      - Awards Ceremony, 1992 (Box 20)
      - Doctors Dickenson and Coon, 1993 (Box 20)
      - Hospital Courtyard Tailgate, 1992 (Box 20)
      - Reunion Lunch, 1992 (Box 20)
      - Visiting Committee, 1994 (Box 20)
    - Medical Center Development
      - 3 females in color/3 females in studio, 1995 (Box 20)
      - 88th Infantry Presentation (Box 20)
      - A.J. French Prof. Dedication, 1995 (Box 20)
      - Alumni
        - Appreciation Dinner, 1995 (Box 20)
        - At Travis Pointe, 1990 (Box 20)
        - Class of 1961 Woodburn, 1990 (Box 20)
        - Group Shots, 1997 (Box 20)
        - Groups, 1996 (Box 20)
        - Luncheon, 1999 (Box 20)
        - Press Conference, Lunch, and Tour, 1996 (Box 20)
        - Registration, 1999 (Box 20)
        - Reunion Luncheon, 1997 (Box 20)
        - Reunion, 1998 (Box 20)
        - Tailgate, 1999 (Box 20)
      - Angen Check Presentation, 1995 (Box 20)
      - Antonia Novella, 1990 (Box 20)
      - Archival Medical Apparatus, 1999 (Box 20)
      - Award and Lunch, 2000 (Box 20)
      - Awards Ceremony, 1999 (Box 20)
      - Bambi Dog Show for Mott, 1996 (Box 20)
      - Benefactors, Mr. Colton, 1989 (Box 20)
      - Bott and Samuels, 1996 (Box 20)
      - Bower Reception Area, 1998 (Box 20)
      - Brandi's Toy Card Valentine's Day, 1995 (Box 20)
      - Breast Cancer Celebrity Dinner, 2000 (Box 20)
      - C. Mounts and Presents, 1996 (Box 20)
      - Cancer Advisory Luncheon, 1990 (Box 20)
      - Carson Book Signing, 1997 (Box 20)
      - Coller Family Plaque Dedication, 1989 (Box 20)
      - CPC Meeting, 1997 (Box 20)
      - Dean Bole with the Foltyns, 1996 (Box 20)
      - Deans Oil Paintings, 2000 (Box 20)
      - Dedication of Carol Holmes Room, 1996 (Box 20)
      - Dickenson's Professorship Reception, 1990 (Box 20)
      - Dr. Austin and Medical Student, 1998 (Box 20)
      - Dr. Barclay with OB/GYN students, 1997 (Box 20)
      - Dr. Barsan at Emergency [Room], 1999 (Box 20)
      - Dr. Dootz and Erin, 1995 (Box 20)
      - Dr. Dunn/Senior Lunch, 1996 (Box 20)
      - Dr. Goldstein with 8th graders, 1997 (Box 20)
      - Dr. Lichter and Mr. Cooper, 1995 (Box 20)
      - Dr. Marletta with students, 1998 (Box 20)
      - Drs. Dunnick and Berg, 1997 (Box 20)
      - Drs. Ginsberg and Lowe, 1997 (Box 20)
      - Drs. Joyce Mitchell and Julie Carol, 1997 (Box 20)
      - Duderstadt and Jobst, 1989 (Box 20)
      - East Medical Center Dinner, 1997 (Box 20)
      - Ed Bove Feature, 2000 (Box 20)
      - Emergency Entrance, 1998 (Box 20)
      - Emeritus Awards, 1995 (Box 20)
      - Ford Library Alumni Dinner, 1997 (Box 20)
      - Garret Dedication, 1989 (Box 20)
      - Ginsberg/Todd Award, 1999 (Box 20)
      - Heart Program Embassadors, 1997 (Box 20)
      - Heutwell, End., 1996 (Box 20)
      - Hewlett Professor, 1998 (Box 20)
      - Historical Medical Thesis, 1999 (Box 20)
      - History of Medicine, Women in Medicine, Tailgate, 1997 (Box 20)
      - Holden Drawing Installation, 1996 (Box 20)
      - Holiday Toy Delivery By Kathy and Dogs, 1995 (Box 20)
      - Hospital Commemorative Plaque, 2000 (Box 20)
      - Huetwell Professor, 1997 (Box 20)
      - Inauguration of Mott Movie Channel, 1995 (Box 20)
      - John Upjohn/Dean Betty, 1998 (Box 21)
      - Judd Group., 1998 (Box 21)
      - Keck Lab, 1995 (Box 21)
      - Kemink Professorship, 1998 (Box 21)
      - Lab Shots, 1995 (Box 21)
      - Lichter Fellowship Award, 1990 (Box 21)
      - Lions Den, 1997 (Box 21)
      - Lozoff and Holmes, 1995 (Box 21)
      - Lu Family, 1998 (Box 21)
      - Macaroni Grill Event, 1998 (Box 21)
      - Macy Professor Inauguration, 1996 (Box 21)
      - Macy Summer Science, 1995 (Box 21)
      - Mardigan Family, 1995 (Box 21)
      - Match Day
        - 1996 (Box 21)
        - 1997 (Box 21)
        - 1998 (Box 21)
      - Matthei Gardens Tour, 1996 (Box 21)
      - Max Wicha Award, 1998 (Box 21)
      - Medical Center Alumni Society (MCAS)
        - Board
          - (Meeting), 1995 (Box 21)
          - 1996 (Box 21)
          - (Spring Board Meeting), 1997 (Box 21)
          - 1998 (Box 21)
        - Career Seminar, 1996 (Box 21)
        - Careers, 1996 (Box 21)
      - MCD Group, 1997 (Box 21)
      - Medical Artifacts, 1999 (Box 21)
      - Medical Illustration (Includes medical illustration group shot), undated (Box 21)
      - Medicine @ Michigan: Products, 1999 (Box 21)
      - MEHI Foundation Group, 1996 (Box 21)
      - MEHI Trustees, 1995 (Box 21)
      - Mel Barclay with students, 1999 (Box 21)
      - Metti Trustees, 1997 (Box 21)
      - Mi. Telephone, 1995 (Box 21)
      - Michigan Magazine, 1999 (Box 21)
      - Millie Schembechler Fundraiser, 1999 (Box 21)
      - Momentum Executive Committee, 1996 (Box 21)
      - Momentum Presentation, 1997 (Box 21)
      - Momentum Tea, 1997 (Box 21)
      - Medical School Graduate Reception, 1999 (Box 21)
      - Medical School Luncheon, 1995 (Box 21)
      - Medicine @ Michigan, Winter 2000 (Box 21)
      - Mott Advisory Board, 1997 (Box 21)
      - Mott Golf Classic
        - 1995 (Box 21)
        - 1998 (Box 21)
      - Mott Golf Outing, 1996 (Box 21)
      - Mott Hospital Courtyard Side, 1996 (Box 21)
      - Mott Hospital Dedication, 1989 (Box 21)
      - Mott Insert Photos, 1996 (Box 21)
      - Mott Printing, 1996 (Box 21)
      - Mott Rock and Roll Party, 1998 (Box 21)
      - Mott Trustees, 1997 (Box 21)
      - Mr. Colton and Students, 1995 (Box 21)
      - MSRB Dedication, 1989 (Box 21)
      - New Horizons in Medicine, 1995 (Box 21)
      - Northwest Airlines VIPs, 1995 (Box 21)
      - Patient and Staff, Juke Box, Ronald McDonald House, 1996 (Box 21)
      - Pharmacia-UpJohn Group, 1996 (Box 21)
      - [Portraits, informal], 1990 (Box 21)
      - Press Conference, 1997 (Box 21)
      - Program in Biomedical Services (PIBS) Students and Staff, 2000 (Box 21)
      - [Reception]
        - [reception], 1990; 2 folders (Box 21)
        - [reception], contact sheet only (Box 21)
      - Reception at Dow Atrium, 1990 (Box 21)
      - Rod and Sandra Campbell, 1995 (Box 21)
      - Ruppenthal Professor Installation Dr. Steven A. Goldstein, 1999 (Box 21)
      - Schembechler Check Presentation, 2000 (Box 21)
      - Schembechlers in Kitchen, 1995 (Box 21)
      - Sellner Awards, 1999 (Box 21)
      - Senator Riegle, 1989 (Box 21)
      - Senior
        - (Luncheon), 1997 (Box 21)
        - (Lunch), 1998 (Box 21)
        - (Luncheon), 1999 (Box 21)
      - Sewall Prof, 1996 (Box 21)
      - Strokes Against Cancer
        - 1995 (Box 21)
        - 1996 (Box 21)
        - 1997 (Box 21)
      - Students and Video Screen, 1997 (Box 21)
      - Survival Flight Team, 1999 (Box 21)
      - Telethon
        - 1989 (Box 21)
        - 1990 (Box 21)
        - 1996 (Box 21)
      - [Tessler], 1990 (Box 21)
      - Tony the Tiger and M&M, 1996 (Box 21)
      - Tony the Tiger, 1995 (Box 21)
      - Townsend Prof, 1996 (Box 21)
      - Transplant Reunion, 1996 (Box 21)
      - [Unidentified], 1990 (Box 21)
      - Vital Signs Seminar, 1990 (Box 21)
      - Vital Signs, 1990 (Box 21)
      - Waggoner Lecture, 1997 (Box 21)
      - Waggoner Lectureship, 1996 (Box 21)
      - White Coat Ceremony
        - 1997 (Box 21)
        - 1998 (Box 21)
      - Wilson Fellowship, 1990 (Box 21)
      - Women in Medicine Tailgate, 1996 (Box 21)
      - Women in Medicine, 1995 (Box 21)
      - Yamada's Reception, 1990 (Box 21)
      - Ypsilanti Shelton Sign, 1999 (Box 21)
    - Medical Center Information Technology (Box 21)
    - Brochure
      - 1995, 2 folders (Box 21)
      - 1996 (Box 21)
    - Medical Illustration, circa 1963 (Box 21)
    - Medical Personnel, 1987 (Box 21)
    - Medical School
      - Black Medical Association Composite, 1992 (Box 21)
      - Bulletin images [c1995 ?], prints (Box 21)
      - M1 Orientation, 1993 (Box 21)
    - Medical School Administration
      - Alpern Lunch, 2001 (Box 21)
      - Alumni (Box 21)
      - Class of '39, 1999 (Box 21)
      - Class of '44, 1999 (Box 21)
      - Class of '49, 1999 (Box 21)
      - Class of '54, 1999 (Box 21)
      - Class of '59, 1999 (Box 21)
      - Class of '64 and '89, 1999 (Box 21)
      - Class of '69, 1999 (Box 21)
      - Class of '74, 1999 (Box 21)
      - Class of '79 and '84, 1999 (Box 21)
      - Baker Lab, 2000 (Box 21)
      - Betsy Lozoff and Rosario Ceballo, 1999 (Box 21)
      - Book Signing, 1999 (Box 21)
      - Books and Books, 1999 (Box 21)
      - Brewer and Merajuer (?), 2000 (Box 21)
      - Brochure, Professional Patient, 2000 (Box 21)
      - Class Pictures in Tunnel, 2000 (Box 21)
      - Dr. John Randolph during interview, 1999 (Box 21)
      - Dr. Joyce Wahr, Magazine Short Story, 1999 (Box 21)
      - Dr. Vorhees and Dr. Fischer in office, 1999 (Box 21)
      - Flowering Trees of Medical School, 2000 (Box 21)
      - Galens Smoker
        - 1999 (Box 21)
        - 2000, 2 folders (Box 21)
      - Graduation, 2000 (Box 21)
      - Hospital and Research Photos, 2000 (Box 21)
      - Judy Wiebelhaus, 2000 (Box 21)
      - Medical School Picnic
        - (Awards), 2000 (Box 21)
        - 2001 (Box 21)
      - New Graduate Students Reception, 1999 (Box 21)
      - Open Books, 1999 (Box 21)
      - Patch Adams, 2000 (Box 21)
      - Patient Simulation, 1999 (Box 21)
      - People on Lab Benches, 1999 (Box 21)
      - Ralph Lydic, 2000 (Box 21)
      - Rowena Matthews and Martha Ludwig, 1999 (Box 22)
      - Scholarship Recipients, 2000 (Box 22)
      - Team Building Games, 2000 (Box 22)
      - Terry Zwolan Cochlear Ear[Implant], 2000 (Box 22)
      - Timeline, Historical Center, 2000 (Box 22)
      - Trans-web Group, 1999 (Box 22)
      - Tribute to 7 Scientists, 2000 (Box 22)
      - Turn of the Century Ribbon Cutting, 2000 (Box 22)
    - Med Sport [Sports Medicine]
      - Boxer and Dietician, 1992 (Box 22)
      - Brochure
        - 1991 (Box 22)
        - 1993 (Box 22)
        - undated (Box 22)
      - Expo, 1992 (Box 22)
      - High Fit Low Fat Cookbook, 1991 (Box 22)
      - Hockey Player Physical, 1994 (Box 22)
      - Ortho Clinic, 1995 (Box 22)
    - Medical Students, undated (Box 22)
    - Medical Television, undated (Box 22)
    - Mental Health and Research Institute (MHRI), 1998 (Box 22)
    - Michigan Alzheimer's Disease Research Center (MADRC), 1993; 1995; 1996 (Box 22)
    - Michigan Diabetes Research and Training Center (MDRTC)
      - Diabetes Research Seminar and Poster Session, 1995 (Box 22)
      - Dr. Cherian and Electron Microscope (Box 22)
      - Gala Event, 1992 (Box 22)
      - NIH Site Visit, 1992 (Box 22)
      - Seminar and Poster Session, 1995 (Box 22)
    - Microbiology
      - Dr. Nairn and Student at/in lab, undated (Box 22)
      - Jove -- Microbiology, 1990 (Box 22)
      - Lab Shots, 1999; 3 folders (Box 22)
      - Nairn/Brochure, 1989 (Box 22)
      - Neihardt Symposium, 2000 (Box 22)
      - Poster Displays, 1989 (Box 22)
      - Silverstein Dissertation Defense, 1991 (Box 22)
    - Mosby
      - Product Shoot, 1998 (Box 22)
    - Mott Children's Hospital
      - Activities, 1990; 1992; undated (Box 22)
      - Board
        - Big Bird Check Presentation, 2000 (Box 22)
        - Football Brunch, 1997 (Box 22)
    - Mott Children's Hospital
      - Christmas Toy Deliver, 1997 (Box 22)
      - Mott/Maternal Care Open House, 1990; negatives (Box 22)
      - New Labor and Delivery Room Interiors, 1995 (Box 22)
    - Nephrology
      - Brochure
        - 1991 (Box 22)
        - 1996 (Box 22)
    - Neurology
      - 1st Annual HSP [hereditary spastic paraplegia]
        - (Evening Shoot), 2000 (Box 22)
        - 2000 (Box 22)
      - Aldrich Portrait Unveiling, 2000 (Box 22)
      - Brochure
        - 1989-1990 (Box 22)
        - 1990 (Box 22)
        - (Residency), 1994 (Box 22)
        - Doug and Judy Collins Neurology Brochure, 2001 (Box 22)
      - Chief Residents Dinner Group, 1996 (Box 22)
      - Clinical Neurophysiology Lab Group, 1996 (Box 22)
      - Doctors with Patient in Wheelchair, 1990 (Box 22)
      - Dr. Beydoun and Resident, 1997 (Box 22)
      - Dr. Casey and Resident, 1997 (Box 22)
      - Feldman Lab Groups, 1998 (Box 22)
      - Feldman, Eva, 1999 (Box 22)
      - Group Shot of Fink Lab, 1996 (Box 22)
      - Group, 1996 (Box 22)
      - Heart Walk, 1999 (Box 22)
      - Herdman Professor, 1997 (Box 22)
      - McDonald Endowment Group, 1995 (Box 22)
      - Sleep Lab, 2000 (Box 22)
    - Neurosurgery
      - Chief Residents Dinner
        - 1995 (Box 22)
        - 2001 (Box 22)
      - Faculty and Residents, 2000 (Box 22)
      - Neurosurgery (negative), undated (Box 22)
      - Resident Dinner
        - 1997 (Box 22)
        - 1998 (Box 22)
    - Nuclear Medicine
      - Columnators for Poster, 1994 (Box 22)
      - Dr. Kuhl Award from D.O.E., 1994 (Box 22)
      - Patient Room and Toilet, 1989 (Box 22)
      - Pet Scanner, 1998 (Box 22)
      - Plaque Awards, 1992 (Box 22)
      - Scanner, 1994 (Box 22)
    - Nurses/Nursing (includes early historical images), circa 1900-1970 (Box 22)
    - Nursing
      - Awards
        - 1997 (Box 22)
        - 1996 (Box 22)
      - Cardiac Crash Cart.1995 (Box 22)
      - CRC Group, 1999 (Box 22)
      - Dermatology Patient Brochure, undated; negatives (Box 22)
      - Display prints, 1990; negatives (Box 22)
      - Dolls, 1993 (Box 22)
      - Exchange, 1991 (Box 22)
      - Friends Christmas Party, 1990 (Box 22)
      - Group
        - 1992 (Box 22)
        - 1997 (Box 22)
      - Horizons
        - Newsletter
          - 1990 (Box 22)
          - (Group Shot), 1992 (Box 22)
        - Magazine
          - Nursing Group 5th Floor, 1990 (Box 22)
        - Summer 1990 (Box 22)
      - Instruments, 1996 (Box 22)
      - Kids Week
        - Art Day, Puppet Show, Trading Places, 1994 (Box 22)
        - Coffee Hour, 1994 (Box 22)
        - With Survival Flight, 1994 (Box 22)
      - Lisa Beckman, 1991; negatives (Box 22)
      - Mott Open House, 1994 (Box 22)
      - Nurses in Motion, 1991; negatives (Box 23)
      - Nursing Anniversary Nurses at Work, undated (Box 23)
      - Pacemakers, 1993 (Box 23)
      - Patient Communication, 1991; negatives (Box 23)
      - Pediatrics Brochure, 1991 (Box 23)
      - Poster
        - (Gift of Life and Sight), 1993 (Box 23)
        - 1997 (Box 23)
      - Psych Nurses, 1990[?] (Box 23)
      - Students, undated; prints and negatives (Box 23)
      - Total Quality Lead Team, 1991; negatives (Box 23)
      - Trach Book, undated (Box 23)
      - Visiting Animals, 1991; negatives (Box 23)
      - Website, 1999; 2 folders (Box 23)
    - Nursing Administration
      - Administration, 1990; 2 folders (Box 23)
      - Barkakauskas Book, 1992 (Box 23)
      - Books, 1995 (Box 23)
      - Nurses at Computer, 1995 (Box 23)
      - Nurses in a Meeting, 1990 (Box 23)
      - Nurses in Action, 1995 (Box 23)
      - Nurses Week, 1995 (Box 23)
      - P3 Nursing Admin, 1990 (Box 23)
    - Nursing Education
      - Check Presentation, 1999 (Box 23)
      - Nurses Week Nominees, 1999 (Box 23)
    - Obstetrics and Gynecology
      - Behrman Endowment, 1999; negatives (Box 23)
      - Dr. Mennon with Plaque Plus Lab, 1998 (Box 23)
      - Dr. Miller and Obstetrics/Gynecology Staff, 1938; undated (Box 23)
      - Installation of the Miller Professorship, 1998 (Box 23)
      - Normal Miller Society, 2001 (Box 23)
      - Norman Miller Presentation, 1999 (Box 23)
      - Obstetrics/Gynecology Travel Club
        - 1950-1975, undated (Box 23)
        - 1985 (Box 23)
    - Office of Construction Management
      - Medical Science I Remodeling, 1996 (Box 23)
      - Patient and Medical Staff Interaction, 1997 (Box 23)
    - Office of Educational Resources and Research
      - Retinopathy Grant Project, 1996 (Box 23)
    - Office of the Vice President for Research
      - Frederick Neidhardt Retirement, 1998 (Box 23)
    - Operating Rooms, 1980; 1981; negatives (Box 23)
    - Ophthalmology
      - "4 Generation Clinic,", 1998 (Box 23)
      - Annual Spring Conference
        - 2000 (Box 23)
        - 2001 (Box 23)
      - "Computer Shots," Drs. Swaroop, Moroi, Richards, 2000 (Box 23)
      - Dr. Hitchcock in Lab, 2000 (Box 23)
      - Dr. Kurz with Laser, 2000 (Box 23)
      - Dr. Lichter and Dr. Richards, 1999 (Box 23)
      - Dr. Sieving in Lab, 2000 (Box 23)
      - Dr. Sugar and Array Machine, 2000 (Box 23)
      - Drs. Sieving, Deretic, and Thompson, 1998 (Box 23)
      - Equipment, 1991 (Box 23)
      - Father and Son: Emotional, 1999 (Box 23)
      - Kellogg Building in, Winter 1999 (Box 23)
      - Kellogg Eye Center Alumni, 1998 (Box 23)
      - Kellogg Eye Center Award and Reception, 1999 (Box 23)
      - Kellogg Eye Center Reunion, 2000 (Box 23)
      - Kellogg Eye Center: Offsite Centers (Livonia Eye Center, West Bloomfield, Brighton Eye Center, 1999 (Box 23)
      - Kellogg Lab, 1999 (Box 23)
      - Kellogg Marketing, 1999 (Box 23)